Finding Aid for the Bruce R. Payne Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series II: Office of the President
  - Series III: Personal Records
    - YWCA at Peabody (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Personal Records
    - Financial Papers (Box 9, Folder 19)